Text,IndividualLabels,CategorizedLabels,llm_labeled_successfully,llm_label,llm_confidence
: Kanye West featuring Jamie Foxx — `` Gold Digger '' ( 2005 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kanye West""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jamie Foxx""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Gold Digger""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Gold Digger""], ""Person"": [""Kanye West"", ""Jamie Foxx""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kanye West', 'start': 2, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jamie Foxx', 'start': 23, 'end': 33}]",0.9996581766807964
Blacktown railway station,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Blacktown railway station""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Blacktown railway station""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Blacktown', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'railway station', 'start': 10, 'end': 25}]",0.9564133311850421
"'' Mycalesis perseus lalassis '' ( Hewitson , 1864 )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Mycalesis perseus lalassis""}]","{""Location"": [""Mycalesis perseus lalassis""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mycalesis perseus lalassis', 'start': 3, 'end': 29}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hewitson', 'start': 35, 'end': 43}]",0.9827667970743091
Jonny Lee Miller - Eli Stone '',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jonny Lee Miller""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Eli Stone""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Eli Stone""], ""Person"": [""Jonny Lee Miller""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Eli Stone', 'start': 19, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jonny Lee Miller', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]",0.991345924942759
Tambourissa cocottensis '' Lorence,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Tambourissa cocottensis""}]","{""Location"": [""Tambourissa cocottensis""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tambourissa cocottensis', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lorence', 'start': 27, 'end': 34}]",0.9707099851847717
Admission to the bar in the United States,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Admission to the bar in the United States""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Admission to the bar in the United States""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'United States', 'start': 28, 'end': 41}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Admission to the bar', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9804055287107293
Willy Unger of 11 .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Willy Unger""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Willy Unger""]}",no,[],0.9942406002998776
"Much construction was undertaken during this period , such as the building of Palermo Cathedral .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Palermo Cathedral""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Palermo Cathedral""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Palermo', 'start': 78, 'end': 85}]",0.9710828598334815
List of The O.C. characters,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""List of The O.C. characters""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""List of The O.C. characters""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of The O.C. characters', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}]",0.9411441864361367
"Cardiff Royal Infirmary , Roath , Cardiff","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Cardiff Royal Infirmary""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Roath , Cardiff""}]","{""Location"": [""Roath , Cardiff""], ""Organization"": [""Cardiff Royal Infirmary""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Cardiff', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Roath', 'start': 26, 'end': 31}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Cardiff', 'start': 34, 'end': 41}]",0.9995029063684988
Roger Houdet 9 June 1958 – 27 May 1959,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Roger Houdet""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Roger Houdet""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Roger Houdet', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]",0.9996245740156922
List of Oz ( TV series ) characters,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""List of Oz ( TV series ) characters""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""List of Oz ( TV series ) characters""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of Oz ( TV series ) characters', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]",0.9209466965105761
: '' Jack and Diane '' by John Mellencamp - '' ( Top 11 ) '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jack and Diane""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Mellencamp""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Jack and Diane""], ""Person"": [""John Mellencamp""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Top 11', 'start': 49, 'end': 55}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jack', 'start': 5, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Diane', 'start': 14, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Mellencamp', 'start': 26, 'end': 41}]",0.9355052832091308
List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Antarctic', 'start': 8, 'end': 17}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'sub-Antarctic', 'start': 22, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands', 'start': 0, 'end': 43}]",0.9718548261644655
Yukon New Democratic Party,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Yukon New Democratic Party""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Yukon New Democratic Party""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Yukon', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Yukon New Democratic Party', 'start': 0, 'end': 26}]",0.976025137729881
1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}]",0.999727293332025
John Reid ( ''27 July 1998 – 17 May 1999 '' ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Reid""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""John Reid""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Reid', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]",0.9995149489533128
Annweiler am Trifels,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Annweiler am Trifels""}]","{""Location"": [""Annweiler am Trifels""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Annweiler am Trifels', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9996795906018363
Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': ""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez"", 'start': 0, 'end': 25}]",0.9962205270265606
`` Moments and Mine '' 7 '' single ( 1981 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Moments and Mine""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Moments and Mine""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Moments and Mine', 'start': 3, 'end': 19}]",0.9050206551429486
2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]",0.9913241254487629
C]] ) ' '' Akritas Chlorakas '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Akritas Chlorakas""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Akritas Chlorakas""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Akritas Chlorakas', 'start': 11, 'end': 28}]",0.9996402965195647
Farmers ' Almanac '' ( 1818–present ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Farmers ' Almanac""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Farmers ' Almanac""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': ""Farmers ' Almanac"", 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.9887986484724945
He was betrayed in 1931 and arrested by the Kuomintang in Tianjin in 1931 .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kuomintang""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Tianjin""}]","{""Location"": [""Tianjin""], ""Organization"": [""Kuomintang""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Tianjin', 'start': 58, 'end': 65}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Kuomintang', 'start': 44, 'end': 54}]",0.9994847119109485
It is found in Peru .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Peru""}]","{""Location"": [""Peru""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Peru', 'start': 15, 'end': 19}]",0.9995938822652912
Steve Hindalong - producer,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Steve Hindalong""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Steve Hindalong""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Steve Hindalong', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}]",0.9991406610600401
Han Suyin gives a detailed account of their overthrow :,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Han Suyin""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Han Suyin""]}",no,[],0.9845365058412733
"Bishop John J. Kinney ( November 9 , 1976 - June 28 , 1982 ) appointed Bishop of Bismarck , Bishop of Saint Cloud ( 1995 )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bishop John J. Kinney""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bishop of Bismarck""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bishop of Saint Cloud""}]","{""Location"": [""Bishop of Bismarck"", ""Bishop of Saint Cloud""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Bishop John J. Kinney""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Bismarck', 'start': 81, 'end': 89}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Saint Cloud', 'start': 102, 'end': 113}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John J. Kinney', 'start': 7, 'end': 21}]",0.9702060893633212
"Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin""}]","{""Location"": [""Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin', 'start': 0, 'end': 38}]",0.9628045294000088
' '' Sydney Theatre Company '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sydney Theatre Company""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sydney Theatre Company""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Sydney Theatre Company', 'start': 5, 'end': 27}]",0.9983555384166649
His first recording of the song was included on his 2005 album Time Well Wasted '' .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Time Well Wasted""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Time Well Wasted""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Time Well Wasted', 'start': 63, 'end': 79}]",0.9092773634712363
Goes to Jhansi ( JHS ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jhansi""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Jhansi""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Jhansi ( JHS )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]",0.9560935674425212
** '' Kashiwa Reysol '' ' 3–2 ( 2–0 ) Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kashiwa Reysol""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Kashiwa Reysol"", ""Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Kashiwa Reysol', 'start': 6, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors', 'start': 38, 'end': 60}]",0.9993097120265068
"He was born in Merritt Island , Florida .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Merritt Island , Florida""}]","{""Location"": [""Merritt Island , Florida""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Merritt Island , Florida', 'start': 15, 'end': 39}]",0.9787369340205344
Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton""}]","{""Location"": [""Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton', 'start': 0, 'end': 38}]",0.9996693795029062
"He scored the first two touchdowns of his career on September 23 , 2007 in a 24–3 win against the St. Louis Rams .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""St. Louis Rams""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""St. Louis Rams""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'St. Louis Rams', 'start': 98, 'end': 112}]",0.9762677083409025
"It was founded in 2013 by Jean Colombera , a member of the Chamber of Deputies that had been elected for the Alternative Democratic Reform Party at the 2009 election .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jean Colombera""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chamber of Deputies""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Alternative Democratic Reform Party""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""2009 election""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Chamber of Deputies"", ""Alternative Democratic Reform Party"", ""2009 election""], ""Person"": [""Jean Colombera""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Alternative Democratic Reform Party', 'start': 109, 'end': 144}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jean Colombera', 'start': 26, 'end': 40}]",0.9951820426364792
Ashley Tappin ( 55.47 ) Erin Phenix ( 56.12 ) Courtney Shealy ( 54.99 ) Amy Van Dyken ( 54.40 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ashley Tappin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Erin Phenix""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Courtney Shealy""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Amy Van Dyken""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ashley Tappin"", ""Erin Phenix"", ""Courtney Shealy"", ""Amy Van Dyken""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ashley Tappin', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Erin Phenix', 'start': 24, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Courtney Shealy', 'start': 46, 'end': 61}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Amy Van Dyken', 'start': 72, 'end': 85}]",0.9997653494998111
Romy Kermer / Rolf Österreich,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Romy Kermer""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Rolf Österreich""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Romy Kermer"", ""Rolf Österreich""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Romy Kermer', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rolf Österreich', 'start': 14, 'end': 29}]",0.9996087168318168
"Gates-Chili High School , Gates","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Gates-Chili High School""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Gates""}]","{""Location"": [""Gates""], ""Organization"": [""Gates-Chili High School""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Gates-Chili High School', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Gates', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]",0.9983038982547384
Riki Lindhome ( 5 appearances ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Riki Lindhome""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Riki Lindhome""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Riki Lindhome', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9997259424534892
Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head""], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.9935656351527125
"He died in Hermanus , Western Cape , South Africa , aged 68 , and was buried in Israel .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Hermanus""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Western Cape""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""South Africa""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Israel""}]","{""Location"": [""Hermanus"", ""Western Cape"", ""South Africa"", ""Israel""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Hermanus , Western Cape , South Africa', 'start': 11, 'end': 49}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Israel', 'start': 80, 'end': 86}]",0.9771005985479084
for the treatment of Type 1 Diabetes .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Type 1 Diabetes""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Type 1 Diabetes""], ""Person"": []}",yes,[],0.9984616510736213
He died at his home at Earls Court and was buried at West Norwood Cemetery .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Earls Court""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""West Norwood Cemetery""}]","{""Location"": [""Earls Court""], ""Organization"": [""West Norwood Cemetery""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Earls Court', 'start': 23, 'end': 34}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'West Norwood Cemetery', 'start': 53, 'end': 74}]",0.9994760823629607
Both teams had the chance to play in Super Bowl XLIX .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Super Bowl XLIX""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Super Bowl XLIX""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Super Bowl XLIX', 'start': 37, 'end': 52}]",0.9994588668568085
Its closest competitor is the Encash Network Service .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Encash Network Service""}]","{""Location"": [""Encash Network Service""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Encash Network Service', 'start': 30, 'end': 52}]",0.999552566786894
"Turning Stone Casino , Verona , New York , United States","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Turning Stone Casino""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Verona , New York""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""United States""}]","{""Location"": [""Verona , New York"", ""United States""], ""Organization"": [""Turning Stone Casino""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Verona , New York , United States', 'start': 23, 'end': 56}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Turning Stone Casino', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9852484739423224
"Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia""}]","{""Location"": [""Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia', 'start': 0, 'end': 41}]",0.9848955594065515
"Tang Yik Chun , Lai Chun Ho , Ng Ka Fung , Tsui Chi Ho","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tang Yik Chun""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lai Chun Ho""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ng Ka Fung""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tsui Chi Ho""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Tang Yik Chun"", ""Lai Chun Ho"", ""Ng Ka Fung"", ""Tsui Chi Ho""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tang Yik Chun', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lai Chun Ho', 'start': 16, 'end': 27}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ng Ka Fung', 'start': 30, 'end': 40}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tsui Chi Ho', 'start': 43, 'end': 54}]",0.9997718550217246
'' 1999 '' ( Prince ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1999""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Prince""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""1999""], ""Person"": [""Prince""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Prince', 'start': 13, 'end': 19}]",0.9994027836821995
Hay River Reserve,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Hay River Reserve""}]","{""Location"": [""Hay River Reserve""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Hay River Reserve', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.9995828142228634
'' Heathcliff '' ( 1980 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Heathcliff""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Heathcliff""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Heathcliff', 'start': 3, 'end': 13}]",0.998870168613853
Galician Academy ( private ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Galician Academy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Galician Academy""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Galician Academy', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]",0.9896128384243681
"'' Thysanoplusia orichalcea '' ( Fabricius , 1775 )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Thysanoplusia orichalcea""}]","{""Location"": [""Thysanoplusia orichalcea""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Fabricius', 'start': 33, 'end': 42}]",0.973689839647706
He became George III 's Chaplain-in-Ordinary .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""George III""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chaplain-in-Ordinary""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""George III"", ""Chaplain-in-Ordinary""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Chaplain-in-Ordinary', 'start': 24, 'end': 44}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'George III', 'start': 10, 'end': 20}]",0.9681608012719369
Mark King ( born 1958 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Mark King""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Mark King""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mark King', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]",0.9994286318230001
Paul Tsongas - 209 ( 4.98   ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Paul Tsongas""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Paul Tsongas""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Paul Tsongas', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]",0.9995203800592907
'' Papilio polyxenes '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Papilio polyxenes""}]","{""Location"": [""Papilio polyxenes""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.9902487785076833
"'' Heliothis nubigera '' Herrich-Schäffer , 1851","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Heliothis nubigera""}]","{""Location"": [""Heliothis nubigera""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Herrich-Schäffer', 'start': 25, 'end': 41}]",0.9892348120610347
' '' Andaman and Nicobar Islands '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Andaman and Nicobar Islands""}]","{""Location"": [""Andaman and Nicobar Islands""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Andaman and Nicobar Islands', 'start': 5, 'end': 32}]",0.9987964875311736
"Glasston , North Dakota","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Glasston , North Dakota""}]","{""Location"": [""Glasston , North Dakota""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Glasston , North Dakota', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9846665408022374
St. Martin River,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""St. Martin River""}]","{""Location"": [""St. Martin River""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'St. Martin River', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]",0.9992513063567701
"The album reached number one halfway through its first week , with over 2,500 copies sold ( rivalling Adele , Bruno Mars and Ed Sheeran ) .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Adele""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bruno Mars""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ed Sheeran""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Adele"", ""Bruno Mars"", ""Ed Sheeran""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Adele', 'start': 102, 'end': 107}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Bruno Mars', 'start': 110, 'end': 120}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ed Sheeran', 'start': 125, 'end': 135}]",0.9996786656726375
Winx Club '' ( 2005–08 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Winx Club""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Winx Club""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Winx Club', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]",0.9601988382794931
"Organized at Fort Craig , it was mustered on 23 November 1861 and served until 28 February 1862 .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Fort Craig""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Fort Craig""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Fort Craig', 'start': 13, 'end': 23}]",0.9994561661712524
Rudy Wurlitzer as Tom O'Folliard,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Rudy Wurlitzer""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tom O'Folliard""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Rudy Wurlitzer"", ""Tom O'Folliard""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rudy Wurlitzer', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': ""Tom O'Folliard"", 'start': 18, 'end': 32}]",0.999802064392771
Conrad Aiken - W. H. Auden - George Barker - John Berryman - Robert Bly - Hart Crane - E. E. Cummings - Donald Davie - James Dickey - H. D . - Keith Douglas - Richard Eberhart - T. S. Eliot - William Empson - David Gascoyne - W. S. Graham - Robert Graves - Thom Gunn - John Heath-Stubbs - Geoffrey Hill - Gerard Manley Hopkins - Ted Hughes - T. E. Hulme - David Jones - Philip Larkin - D. H. Lawrence - Denise Levertov - C. Day Lewis - Robert Lowell - Norman MacCaig - Hugh MacDiarmid - Louis MacNeice - Charles Madge - W. S. Merwin - Christopher Middleton - Harold Monro - Marianne Moore - Edwin Muir - Howard Nemerov - Charles Olson - Wilfred Owen - Sylvia Plath - Ezra Pound - F. T. Prince - Kathleen Raine - John Crowe Ransom - Herbert Read - Laura Riding - Anne Ridler - Michael Roberts - Theodore Roethke - Isaac Rosenberg - Louis Simpson - Edith Sitwell - W. D. Snodgrass - Stephen Spender - Wallace Stevens - Allen Tate - Dylan Thomas - R. S. Thomas - Charles Tomlinson - Vernon Watkins - Richard Wilbur - William Carlos Williams - James Wright - W. B. Yeats,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Conrad Aiken""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. H. Auden""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""George Barker""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Berryman""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Bly""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hart Crane""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""E.""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""E. Cummings""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Donald Davie""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""James Dickey""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""H. D .""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Keith Douglas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Richard Eberhart""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""T. S. Eliot""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William Empson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""David Gascoyne""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. S. Graham""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Graves""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thom Gunn""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Heath-Stubbs""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Geoffrey Hill""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Gerard Manley Hopkins""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ted Hughes""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""T. E. Hulme""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""David Jones""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Philip Larkin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""D. H. Lawrence""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Denise Levertov""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""C. Day Lewis""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Lowell""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Norman MacCaig""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hugh MacDiarmid""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Louis MacNeice""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Madge""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. S. Merwin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Christopher Middleton""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Harold Monro""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Marianne Moore""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Edwin Muir""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Howard Nemerov""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Olson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wilfred Owen""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sylvia Plath""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ezra Pound""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""F. T. Prince""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kathleen Raine""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Crowe Ransom""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Herbert Read""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Laura Riding""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Anne Ridler""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Michael Roberts""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Theodore Roethke""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Isaac Rosenberg""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Louis Simpson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Edith Sitwell""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. D. Snodgrass""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Stephen Spender""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wallace Stevens""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Allen Tate""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Dylan Thomas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""R. S. Thomas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Tomlinson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Vernon Watkins""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Richard Wilbur""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William Carlos Williams""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""James Wright""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. B. Yeats""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""H. D ."", ""C. Day Lewis""], ""Person"": [""Conrad Aiken"", ""W. H. Auden"", ""George Barker"", ""John Berryman"", ""Robert Bly"", ""Hart Crane"", ""E."", ""E. Cummings"", ""Donald Davie"", ""James Dickey"", ""Keith Douglas"", ""Richard Eberhart"", ""T. S. Eliot"", ""William Empson"", ""David Gascoyne"", ""W. S. Graham"", ""Robert Graves"", ""Thom Gunn"", ""John Heath-Stubbs"", ""Geoffrey Hill"", ""Gerard Manley Hopkins"", ""Ted Hughes"", ""T. E. Hulme"", ""David Jones"", ""Philip Larkin"", ""D. H. Lawrence"", ""Denise Levertov"", ""Robert Lowell"", ""Norman MacCaig"", ""Hugh MacDiarmid"", ""Louis MacNeice"", ""Charles Madge"", ""W. S. Merwin"", ""Christopher Middleton"", ""Harold Monro"", ""Marianne Moore"", ""Edwin Muir"", ""Howard Nemerov"", ""Charles Olson"", ""Wilfred Owen"", ""Sylvia Plath"", ""Ezra Pound"", ""F. T. Prince"", ""Kathleen Raine"", ""John Crowe Ransom"", ""Herbert Read"", ""Laura Riding"", ""Anne Ridler"", ""Michael Roberts"", ""Theodore Roethke"", ""Isaac Rosenberg"", ""Louis Simpson"", ""Edith Sitwell"", ""W. D. Snodgrass"", ""Stephen Spender"", ""Wallace Stevens"", ""Allen Tate"", ""Dylan Thomas"", ""R. S. Thomas"", ""Charles Tomlinson"", ""Vernon Watkins"", ""Richard Wilbur"", ""William Carlos Williams"", ""James Wright"", ""W. B. Yeats""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Conrad Aiken', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. H. Auden', 'start': 15, 'end': 26}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'George Barker', 'start': 29, 'end': 42}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Berryman', 'start': 45, 'end': 58}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Bly', 'start': 61, 'end': 71}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hart Crane', 'start': 74, 'end': 84}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'E. E. Cummings', 'start': 87, 'end': 101}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Donald Davie', 'start': 104, 'end': 116}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'James Dickey', 'start': 119, 'end': 131}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'H. D.', 'start': 134, 'end': 139}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Keith Douglas', 'start': 143, 'end': 156}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Richard Eberhart', 'start': 159, 'end': 175}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'T. S. Eliot', 'start': 178, 'end': 189}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William Empson', 'start': 192, 'end': 206}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'David Gascoyne', 'start': 209, 'end': 223}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. S. Graham', 'start': 226, 'end': 238}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Graves', 'start': 241, 'end': 254}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thom Gunn', 'start': 257, 'end': 266}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Heath-Stubbs', 'start': 269, 'end': 286}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Geoffrey Hill', 'start': 289, 'end': 302}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Gerard Manley Hopkins', 'start': 305, 'end': 326}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ted Hughes', 'start': 329, 'end': 339}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'T. E. Hulme', 'start': 342, 'end': 353}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'David Jones', 'start': 356, 'end': 367}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Philip Larkin', 'start': 370, 'end': 383}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'D. H. Lawrence', 'start': 386, 'end': 400}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Denise Levertov', 'start': 403, 'end': 418}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'C. Day Lewis', 'start': 421, 'end': 433}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Lowell', 'start': 436, 'end': 449}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Norman MacCaig', 'start': 452, 'end': 466}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hugh MacDiarmid', 'start': 469, 'end': 484}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Louis MacNeice', 'start': 487, 'end': 501}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Madge', 'start': 504, 'end': 517}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. S. Merwin', 'start': 520, 'end': 532}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Christopher Middleton', 'start': 535, 'end': 556}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Harold Monro', 'start': 559, 'end': 571}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Marianne Moore', 'start': 574, 'end': 588}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Edwin Muir', 'start': 591, 'end': 601}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Howard Nemerov', 'start': 604, 'end': 618}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Olson', 'start': 621, 'end': 634}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wilfred Owen', 'start': 637, 'end': 649}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sylvia Plath', 'start': 652, 'end': 664}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ezra Pound', 'start': 667, 'end': 677}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'F. T. Prince', 'start': 680, 'end': 692}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kathleen Raine', 'start': 695, 'end': 709}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Crowe Ransom', 'start': 712, 'end': 729}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Herbert Read', 'start': 732, 'end': 744}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Laura Riding', 'start': 747, 'end': 759}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Anne Ridler', 'start': 762, 'end': 773}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Michael Roberts', 'start': 776, 'end': 791}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Theodore Roethke', 'start': 794, 'end': 810}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Isaac Rosenberg', 'start': 813, 'end': 828}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Louis Simpson', 'start': 831, 'end': 844}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Edith Sitwell', 'start': 847, 'end': 860}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. D. Snodgrass', 'start': 863, 'end': 878}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Stephen Spender', 'start': 881, 'end': 896}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wallace Stevens', 'start': 899, 'end': 914}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Allen Tate', 'start': 917, 'end': 927}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Dylan Thomas', 'start': 930, 'end': 942}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'R. S. Thomas', 'start': 945, 'end': 957}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Tomlinson', 'start': 960, 'end': 977}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Vernon Watkins', 'start': 980, 'end': 994}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Richard Wilbur', 'start': 997, 'end': 1011}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William Carlos Williams', 'start': 1014, 'end': 1037}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'James Wright', 'start': 1040, 'end': 1052}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. B. Yeats', 'start': 1055, 'end': 1066}]",0.9991948975165607
*Seated figure of Sir Walter Scott for Powderham Castle ( 1832 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Sir Walter Scott""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Powderham Castle""}]","{""Location"": [""Powderham Castle""], ""Organization"": [""Sir Walter Scott""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Powderham Castle', 'start': 39, 'end': 55}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sir Walter Scott', 'start': 18, 'end': 34}]",0.9994491617384941
"Sandy Ridge , North Carolina","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Sandy Ridge , North Carolina""}]","{""Location"": [""Sandy Ridge , North Carolina""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Sandy Ridge , North Carolina', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]",0.9840167569861263
Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor )""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ashok Kumar', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}]",0.9252344787097244
Thomas Gabriel Fischer leaves Celtic Frost in April .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thomas Gabriel Fischer""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Celtic Frost""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Celtic Frost""], ""Person"": [""Thomas Gabriel Fischer""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Celtic Frost', 'start': 30, 'end': 42}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thomas Gabriel Fischer', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}]",0.9883358554711863
'' Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ? '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ?""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ?""], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.9797512010786089
Otto Geßler ( Acting ) ( 1875–1955 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Otto Geßler""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Otto Geßler""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Acting', 'start': 14, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Otto Geßler', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}]",0.977141085272968
: On Lifetime Channel,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Lifetime Channel""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Lifetime Channel""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Lifetime Channel', 'start': 5, 'end': 21}]",0.9946889722748204
RCI 367 ( Radio Canada International ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Radio Canada International""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Radio Canada International""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'RCI 367', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Radio Canada International', 'start': 10, 'end': 36}]",0.9969791374208582
"Sir Robert Robinson , from 1930 to 1954 .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sir Robert Robinson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sir Robert Robinson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sir Robert Robinson', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]",0.9997189459864144
"Hutton , Frederick Wollaston .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hutton , Frederick Wollaston""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Hutton , Frederick Wollaston""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hutton', 'start': 0, 'end': 6}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Frederick Wollaston', 'start': 9, 'end': 28}]",0.9987656477106649
'' Macrobathra monoclina '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Macrobathra monoclina""}]","{""Location"": [""Macrobathra monoclina""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.7724813089785306
He one of eleven founding members of the American Society of Landscape Architects in 1899 and was active in the City Beautiful Movement '' .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""American Society of Landscape Architects""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""City Beautiful Movement""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""American Society of Landscape Architects"", ""City Beautiful Movement""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'American Society of Landscape Architects', 'start': 41, 'end': 81}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'City Beautiful Movement', 'start': 112, 'end': 135}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'He', 'start': 0, 'end': 2}]",0.9985733948082334
"Alberto Mancini won in the final 7–5 , 2–6 , 7–6 , 7–5 against Boris Becker .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Alberto Mancini""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Boris Becker""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Alberto Mancini"", ""Boris Becker""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Alberto Mancini', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Boris Becker', 'start': 63, 'end': 75}]",0.9998472074629234
'' Congoharpax aberrans '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Congoharpax aberrans""}]","{""Location"": [""Congoharpax aberrans""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.6632397634548098
Kaohsiung Museum of Labor,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kaohsiung Museum of Labor""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Kaohsiung Museum of Labor""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Kaohsiung', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Museum of Labor', 'start': 10, 'end': 25}]",0.9643180027085106
"Benigno S. Aquino , Jr . , August 21 , 2004 ( posthumous )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Benigno S. Aquino , Jr .""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Benigno S. Aquino , Jr .""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Benigno S. Aquino , Jr.', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9285664845024169
Lina Carstens ( 1892–1978 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lina Carstens""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Lina Carstens""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lina Carstens', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9997381490327075
"**On June 26 against the Chicago Cubs , he got his 2000th career hit with a home run in the second inning .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chicago Cubs""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Chicago Cubs""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Chicago Cubs', 'start': 25, 'end': 37}]",0.8762982786227981
Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 46}]",0.9997801922610463
Carmelita Tropicana - Performance artist,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Carmelita Tropicana""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Carmelita Tropicana""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Carmelita Tropicana', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]",0.9989133472276045
University of Giessen,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""University of Giessen""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""University of Giessen""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'University of Giessen', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}]",0.9713090200452752
Bradley Beal ( 34 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bradley Beal""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Bradley Beal""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Bradley Beal', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]",0.9989459118272181
"Five Borders shops in Oxford Street , Llantrisant , Blanchardstown , Swindon and London Colney were closed in July 2009 and replaced by New Look .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Oxford Street""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Llantrisant""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Blanchardstown""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Swindon""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""London Colney""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""New Look""}]","{""Location"": [""Llantrisant"", ""Blanchardstown"", ""Swindon"", ""London Colney""], ""Organization"": [""Oxford Street"", ""New Look""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Oxford Street', 'start': 22, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Llantrisant', 'start': 38, 'end': 49}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Blanchardstown', 'start': 52, 'end': 66}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Swindon', 'start': 69, 'end': 76}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'London Colney', 'start': 81, 'end': 94}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Five Borders', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'New Look', 'start': 136, 'end': 144}]",0.9731199321990742
"Lord Zetland , the Secretary of State for India , was presiding over the meeting and was wounded .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lord Zetland""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Secretary of State for India""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Secretary of State for India""], ""Person"": [""Lord Zetland""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lord Zetland', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Secretary of State for India', 'start': 19, 'end': 47}]",0.99824203600547
Night At The Museum,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Night At The Museum""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Night At The Museum""], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.5920158830391566
Vepris trifoliolata '' ( Engl .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Vepris trifoliolata""}]","{""Location"": [""Vepris trifoliolata""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.7333713307405261
** `` Back for More '' – Sandwich,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Sandwich""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Sandwich""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Back for More', 'start': 6, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sandwich', 'start': 25, 'end': 33}]",0.9546529990978896
"Crested caracara , ''Caracara cheriway '' ( A )","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Crested caracara""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Crested caracara""], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.891371376241453
"8 July — Annie Shepherd Swan , writer ( died 1943 )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Annie Shepherd Swan""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Annie Shepherd Swan""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Annie Shepherd Swan', 'start': 9, 'end': 28}]",0.999199942596202
Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Vandino', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ugolino Vivaldi', 'start': 12, 'end': 27}]",0.9997867306608668
Inhaler ( album ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Inhaler ( album )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Inhaler ( album )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Inhaler ( album )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]",0.9927429567274108
"'' Autosticha pelodes '' Meyrick , 1928","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Autosticha pelodes""}]","{""Location"": [""Autosticha pelodes""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Meyrick', 'start': 25, 'end': 32}]",0.9365186170947567
Cities Built on Sand,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Cities Built on Sand""}]","{""Location"": [""Cities Built on Sand""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.9907784863659272
"It was originally recorded by The Great Society , and later by Jefferson Airplane .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""The Great Society""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jefferson Airplane""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""The Great Society"", ""Jefferson Airplane""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'The Great Society', 'start': 30, 'end': 47}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Jefferson Airplane', 'start': 63, 'end': 81}]",0.9989964038731558
H. T. Bartlett 1947–1949,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""H. T. Bartlett""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""H. T. Bartlett""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'H. T. Bartlett', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}]",0.9975010764950516
' '' Mittani '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Mittani""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Mittani""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mittani', 'start': 5, 'end': 12}]",0.9885496572963145
Its local government area are the Cities of Boroondara and Stonnington .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""local government area""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Boroondara""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Stonnington""}]","{""Location"": [""Boroondara"", ""Stonnington""], ""Organization"": [""local government area""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Boroondara', 'start': 44, 'end': 54}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Stonnington', 'start': 59, 'end': 70}]",0.9405806232914888
Martín de Ursúa,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Martín de Ursúa""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Martín de Ursúa""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Martín de Ursúa', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}]",0.9995836481402262
"Zawadzkie , Kolonowskie , Leśnica , Ujazd","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Zawadzkie""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Kolonowskie""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Leśnica""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Ujazd""}]","{""Location"": [""Zawadzkie"", ""Kolonowskie"", ""Leśnica"", ""Ujazd""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Zawadzkie', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Kolonowskie', 'start': 12, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Leśnica', 'start': 26, 'end': 33}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Ujazd', 'start': 36, 'end': 41}]",0.999558357626643
"Orange , New South Wales","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Orange , New South Wales""}]","{""Location"": [""Orange , New South Wales""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Orange , New South Wales', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}]",0.9939243250061915
"Göttingen State and University Library , Göttingen","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Göttingen State and University Library""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Göttingen""}]","{""Location"": [""Göttingen""], ""Organization"": [""Göttingen State and University Library""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Göttingen', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Göttingen State and University Library', 'start': 0, 'end': 38}]",0.9994371309659762
' '' Uganda '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Uganda""}]","{""Location"": [""Uganda""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Uganda', 'start': 5, 'end': 11}]",0.9994122719526305
Dwarf flying fox,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Dwarf flying fox""}]","{""Location"": [""Dwarf flying fox""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.737758023192244
"In 1989 , he joined Rapho agency and spent one year in Egypt .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Rapho agency""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Egypt""}]","{""Location"": [""Egypt""], ""Organization"": [""Rapho agency""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Egypt', 'start': 55, 'end': 60}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Rapho agency', 'start': 20, 'end': 32}]",0.9985938307170388
Ruth Bryan Owen was also a granddaughter .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ruth Bryan Owen""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ruth Bryan Owen""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ruth Bryan Owen', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}]",0.9996899957802412
Skegness Town A.F.C .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Skegness Town A.F.C .""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Skegness Town A.F.C .""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Skegness Town A.F.C.', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9462173723739078
"Horisme aquata '' ( Hübner , 1813 )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Horisme aquata""}]","{""Location"": [""Horisme aquata""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Horisme aquata', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hübner', 'start': 20, 'end': 26}]",0.9986892506807326
The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles '',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}]",0.9955925027029501
Matthias Bachinger Ričardas Berankis Niels Desein Pere Riba,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Matthias Bachinger""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ričardas Berankis""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Niels Desein""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Pere Riba""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Matthias Bachinger"", ""Ričardas Berankis"", ""Niels Desein"", ""Pere Riba""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Matthias Bachinger', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ričardas Berankis', 'start': 19, 'end': 36}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Niels Desein', 'start': 37, 'end': 49}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Pere Riba', 'start': 50, 'end': 59}]",0.9997952167098719
Little River ( Cariboo River ),"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Little River ( Cariboo River )""}]","{""Location"": [""Little River ( Cariboo River )""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Little River', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Cariboo River', 'start': 15, 'end': 28}]",0.9992057485657839
"Grangettes , Marsens , Sâles , Riaz","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Grangettes""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Marsens""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Sâles""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Riaz""}]","{""Location"": [""Grangettes"", ""Marsens"", ""Sâles"", ""Riaz""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Grangettes', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Marsens', 'start': 13, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sâles', 'start': 23, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Riaz', 'start': 31, 'end': 35}]",0.9996862893982337
The Little Mermaid 2 : Return to the Sea '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""The Little Mermaid 2 : Return to the Sea""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""The Little Mermaid 2 : Return to the Sea""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'The Little Mermaid 2 : Return to the Sea', 'start': 0, 'end': 40}]",0.9653798104105685
": Ross Dowson - 4,539","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ross Dowson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ross Dowson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ross Dowson', 'start': 2, 'end': 13}]",0.9867402252567156
`` Dead on Arrival '' - Fall Out Boy,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Dead on Arrival""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Fall Out Boy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Dead on Arrival"", ""Fall Out Boy""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Fall Out Boy', 'start': 24, 'end': 36}]",0.9361217102761846
Lists of violinists,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lists of violinists""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Lists of violinists""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Lists of violinists', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]",0.8925174883676357
SPÖ ( 'Labour ' ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""SPÖ""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""SPÖ""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'SPÖ', 'start': 0, 'end': 3}]",0.8352562686510772
' '' Trisha Chetty '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Trisha Chetty""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Trisha Chetty""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Trisha Chetty', 'start': 5, 'end': 18}]",0.9978479886029956
Harry Gordon ( disambiguation ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Harry Gordon ( disambiguation )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Harry Gordon ( disambiguation )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Harry Gordon', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]",0.991832436364642
Axtell High School ( disambiguation ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Axtell High School ( disambiguation )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Axtell High School ( disambiguation )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Axtell High School', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}]",0.9660875713666774
St. Louis Wrestling Hall of Fame,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""St. Louis Wrestling Hall of Fame""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""St. Louis Wrestling Hall of Fame""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'St. Louis', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Wrestling Hall of Fame', 'start': 10, 'end': 32}]",0.9802357268396112
Cultural heritage sites in FATA,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Cultural heritage sites in FATA""}]","{""Location"": [""Cultural heritage sites in FATA""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'FATA', 'start': 27, 'end': 31}]",0.9995064863471437
William Joseph McInnes Botanic Garden and Campus Arboretum,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""William Joseph McInnes Botanic Garden and Campus Arboretum""}]","{""Location"": [""William Joseph McInnes Botanic Garden and Campus Arboretum""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'William Joseph McInnes Botanic Garden and Campus Arboretum', 'start': 0, 'end': 58}]",0.9868072503759197
1st King 's Dragoon Guards '' ( from 26 February until 22 March 1941 ) '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1st King 's Dragoon Guards""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""1st King 's Dragoon Guards""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': ""1st King 's Dragoon Guards"", 'start': 0, 'end': 26}]",0.9927777367503912
** Wang Zhaozuo ( 王昭祚 ) ( killed by Zhang Wenli 921 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wang Zhaozuo""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Zhang Wenli""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Wang Zhaozuo"", ""Zhang Wenli""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wang Zhaozuo', 'start': 3, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Zhang Wenli', 'start': 36, 'end': 47}]",0.9986165213731839
"George , Duke of Saxony , 1471 – 1539","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""George , Duke of Saxony""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""George , Duke of Saxony""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Saxony', 'start': 17, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'George , Duke of Saxony', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9459051194721639
Borough of Bedford,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Borough of Bedford""}]","{""Location"": [""Borough of Bedford""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Borough of Bedford', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}]",0.9633482231499157
Feliks Kazimierz Potocki ( 1682 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Feliks Kazimierz Potocki""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Feliks Kazimierz Potocki""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Feliks Kazimierz Potocki', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}]",0.9997238091661326
Imre Nagy ( 1896–1958 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Imre Nagy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Imre Nagy""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Imre Nagy', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]",0.9996764701845616
Trawlers of the Royal Navy,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Trawlers of the Royal Navy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Trawlers of the Royal Navy""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Royal Navy', 'start': 16, 'end': 26}]",0.9033624105223665
James Scullin ( 22 October 1929 – 6 January 1932 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""James Scullin""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""James Scullin""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'James Scullin', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9997298917482327
"Macaria granitata '' – Guenée , 1857 - Granite Moth","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Macaria granitata""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Guenée""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Granite Moth""}]","{""Location"": [""Macaria granitata""], ""Organization"": [""Granite Moth""], ""Person"": [""Guenée""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Macaria granitata', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Guenée', 'start': 23, 'end': 29}]",0.9543676349166725
"'' Pyrausta virginalis '' Duponchel , 1832","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Pyrausta virginalis""}]","{""Location"": [""Pyrausta virginalis""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Duponchel', 'start': 26, 'end': 35}]",0.9137719788127635
"Colebrookdale Township , Berks County , Pennsylvania","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Colebrookdale Township , Berks County , Pennsylvania""}]","{""Location"": [""Colebrookdale Township , Berks County , Pennsylvania""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Colebrookdale Township', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Berks County', 'start': 25, 'end': 37}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Pennsylvania', 'start': 40, 'end': 52}]",0.9994171239112642
Matthew Farhang Mohtadi,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Matthew Farhang Mohtadi""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Matthew Farhang Mohtadi""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Matthew Farhang Mohtadi', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9997242986081781
911th Air Refueling Squadron : 30 September 1982 – 22 April 1991,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""911th Air Refueling Squadron""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""911th Air Refueling Squadron""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '911th Air Refueling Squadron', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]",0.9996425048438271
Communes of the Territoire de Belfort department,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Communes of the Territoire de Belfort department""}]","{""Location"": [""Communes of the Territoire de Belfort department""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Territoire de Belfort', 'start': 16, 'end': 37}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Communes', 'start': 0, 'end': 8}]",0.9207369944620873
Francisco Espoz y Mina,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Francisco Espoz y Mina""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Francisco Espoz y Mina""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Francisco Espoz y Mina', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}]",0.9998145087404914
' '' Crazy Love Tour '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Crazy Love Tour""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Crazy Love Tour""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Crazy Love Tour', 'start': 5, 'end': 20}]",0.9824088732608357
: Chief Justice of Nepal,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chief Justice of Nepal""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Chief Justice of Nepal""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Nepal', 'start': 19, 'end': 24}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Chief Justice', 'start': 2, 'end': 15}]",0.9992309112449621
: Big FM ( 7.74   ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Big FM""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Big FM""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Big FM', 'start': 2, 'end': 8}]",0.9956648067791375
It is from the Pathanamthitta district headquarters .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Pathanamthitta district""}]","{""Location"": [""Pathanamthitta district""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Pathanamthitta district', 'start': 15, 'end': 38}]",0.9276398230770407
13 Kevin Riley - ''Freshman '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kevin Riley""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Kevin Riley""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kevin Riley', 'start': 3, 'end': 14}]",0.9931005439119064
Its headquarters are in Guatemala City .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Guatemala City""}]","{""Location"": [""Guatemala City""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Guatemala City', 'start': 24, 'end': 38}]",0.9997487238473848
Rumba]] / `` Waiting on the World to Change '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Waiting on the World to Change""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Waiting on the World to Change""], ""Person"": []}",yes,[],0.9329436001145184
She later slept with Charlotte Lau ( Amy Yamazaki ) .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charlotte Lau""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Amy Yamazaki""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Charlotte Lau"", ""Amy Yamazaki""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charlotte Lau', 'start': 21, 'end': 34}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Amy Yamazaki', 'start': 37, 'end': 49}]",0.9983730014326568
Armani Jeans Milano 68–72 Khimki Moscow Region,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Armani Jeans Milano""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Khimki Moscow Region""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Armani Jeans Milano"", ""Khimki Moscow Region""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Milano', 'start': 13, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Moscow Region', 'start': 33, 'end': 46}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Armani Jeans', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Khimki', 'start': 26, 'end': 32}]",0.9653077310018371
( with Daniel Ryan ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Daniel Ryan""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Daniel Ryan""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Daniel Ryan', 'start': 7, 'end': 18}]",0.8878590425801475
Sara C. Bisel,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sara C. Bisel""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sara C. Bisel""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sara C. Bisel', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9997164640643131
She was launched in 1936 and was sunk during the Second World War .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Second World War""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Second World War""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'She', 'start': 0, 'end': 3}]",0.998381917394525
William B. Buffum,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William B. Buffum""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""William B. Buffum""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William B. Buffum', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.999705954022745
'' Daddy at Home '' 企鹅爸爸,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Daddy at Home""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Daddy at Home""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Daddy at Home', 'start': 3, 'end': 16}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': '企鹅爸爸', 'start': 20, 'end': 24}]",0.9442242373018896
"He was a member of the Maine House of Representatives in 1862 , 1864 , 1866 and 1872 and was a delegate to the Republican National Convention in 1864 .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Maine House of Representatives""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Republican National Convention""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Maine House of Representatives"", ""Republican National Convention""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Maine', 'start': 23, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Republican National Convention', 'start': 111, 'end': 141}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'He', 'start': 0, 'end': 2}]",0.9735250259500483
20px ' '' Starachowice '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Starachowice""}]","{""Location"": [""Starachowice""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[],0.6738897143629888
Szema Wah Lung as Baijun,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Szema Wah Lung""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Szema Wah Lung""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Szema Wah Lung', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Baijun', 'start': 18, 'end': 24}]",0.9997459016262615
: Paul Nicholson '' ( Third round ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Paul Nicholson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Paul Nicholson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Paul Nicholson', 'start': 2, 'end': 16}]",0.999348795427794
"`` I Want More '' ( Can song ) , a 1976 song by Can","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""`` I Want More '' ( Can song )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""`` I Want More '' ( Can song )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Can song', 'start': 20, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Can', 'start': 20, 'end': 23}]",0.9134430943473537
"It originated in Jamaica , North America and Europe , and first became popular in the late 1990s .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Jamaica""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""North America""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Europe""}]","{""Location"": [""Jamaica"", ""North America"", ""Europe""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Jamaica', 'start': 17, 'end': 24}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'North America', 'start': 27, 'end': 40}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Europe', 'start': 45, 'end': 51}]",0.9996593427965126
KKCEM Dhanbad was established in the year of 2011 .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Dhanbad""}]","{""Location"": [""Dhanbad""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Dhanbad', 'start': 6, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'KKCEM', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]",0.9985399884861236
"The survivors were put ashore at Karlskrona , Sweden .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Karlskrona""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Sweden""}]","{""Location"": [""Karlskrona"", ""Sweden""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Karlskrona , Sweden', 'start': 33, 'end': 52}]",0.9861947704854411
J. H. Hobart Ward,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""J. H. Hobart Ward""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""J. H. Hobart Ward""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'J. H. Hobart Ward', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.9981749745479428
Thomas Langdon Grace,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thomas Langdon Grace""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Thomas Langdon Grace""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thomas Langdon Grace', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9996921399440639
Stephen Levin ( councillor ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Stephen Levin ( councillor )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Stephen Levin ( councillor )""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Stephen Levin', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9498001279429275
Ilinka Mitreva ( 2002-2006 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ilinka Mitreva""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ilinka Mitreva""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ilinka Mitreva', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}]",0.999716903337853
Charlie Brown tries to sell wreaths door-to-door .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charlie Brown""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Charlie Brown""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charlie Brown', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9995736381840427
"Przerębska Huta , Kościerzyna County","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Przerębska Huta , Kościerzyna County""}]","{""Location"": [""Przerębska Huta , Kościerzyna County""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Przerębska Huta', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Kościerzyna County', 'start': 18, 'end': 36}]",0.9995846488374983
"New York 2,372,949 ( 12.1   )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""New York""}]","{""Location"": [""New York""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'New York', 'start': 0, 'end': 8}]",0.994785633712356
' '' Elton John '' ' and ' '' Kiki Dee '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Elton John""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kiki Dee""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Elton John"", ""Kiki Dee""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Elton John', 'start': 5, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kiki Dee', 'start': 30, 'end': 38}]",0.9995802796620133
Stephen Kosgei Kibet,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Stephen Kosgei Kibet""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Stephen Kosgei Kibet""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Stephen Kosgei Kibet', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]",0.9996983184077125
"Takko , Aomori Prefecture","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Takko""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Aomori Prefecture""}]","{""Location"": [""Aomori Prefecture""], ""Organization"": [""Takko""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Aomori Prefecture', 'start': 8, 'end': 25}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Takko', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]",0.9704016763203728
"Stadion v Jiráskově ulici , Jihlava","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Stadion v Jiráskově ulici""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Jihlava""}]","{""Location"": [""Jihlava""], ""Organization"": [""Stadion v Jiráskově ulici""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Stadion v Jiráskově ulici , Jihlava', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}]",0.9564011339315877
Wayne Dowdy ( D ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wayne Dowdy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Wayne Dowdy""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wayne Dowdy', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}]",0.9962370234097846
"He was born in Bobai County , Guangxi .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bobai County""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Guangxi""}]","{""Location"": [""Bobai County"", ""Guangxi""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Bobai County , Guangxi', 'start': 15, 'end': 37}]",0.9813819682952051
"South Windsor , Connecticut","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""South Windsor , Connecticut""}]","{""Location"": [""South Windsor , Connecticut""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'South Windsor , Connecticut', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}]",0.9843089866952152
Communes of the Côte-d'Or department,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Communes of the Côte-d'Or department""}]","{""Location"": [""Communes of the Côte-d'Or department""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': ""Côte-d'Or"", 'start': 16, 'end': 25}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': ""Communes of the Côte-d'Or department"", 'start': 0, 'end': 36}]",0.958132224514809
Njenga Karume ( 2006 ? -2008 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Njenga Karume""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Njenga Karume""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Njenga Karume', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9997289132895192
'' Holy Roman Empire '' ' – Leopold I ( 1658–1705 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Holy Roman Empire""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Leopold I""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Holy Roman Empire""], ""Person"": [""Leopold I""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Holy Roman Empire', 'start': 3, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Leopold I', 'start': 28, 'end': 37}]",0.9809676472859719
The text was first edited by Gershom Scholem ( 1965 ) .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Gershom Scholem""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Gershom Scholem""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Gershom Scholem', 'start': 29, 'end': 44}]",0.9995540545471572
Gregoria de Jesús ( 1978 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Gregoria de Jesús""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Gregoria de Jesús""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Gregoria de Jesús', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.9996357496020399
It flows from Ägerisee through Lake Zug into the Reuss .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Ägerisee""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Lake Zug""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Reuss""}]","{""Location"": [""Ägerisee"", ""Lake Zug"", ""Reuss""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Ägerisee', 'start': 14, 'end': 22}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Lake Zug', 'start': 31, 'end': 39}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Reuss', 'start': 49, 'end': 54}]",0.9994274676716312
Epoch of Unlight,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Epoch of Unlight""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Epoch of Unlight""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Epoch of Unlight', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]",0.998002551350514
Rick Rubin - producer,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Rick Rubin""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Rick Rubin""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rick Rubin', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}]",0.9984536690835802
*August 15 – Mary Lou Graham,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Mary Lou Graham""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Mary Lou Graham""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mary Lou Graham', 'start': 13, 'end': 28}]",0.9995331318508667
"Joseph Benavidez , Head Coach","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Joseph Benavidez""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Joseph Benavidez""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Joseph Benavidez', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Head Coach', 'start': 19, 'end': 29}]",0.9996606742704467
"*Ambassador to Egypt , Sudan and the Arab League : 1963–1970","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Egypt""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Sudan""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Arab League""}]","{""Location"": [""Egypt"", ""Sudan""], ""Organization"": [""Arab League""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Egypt', 'start': 15, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Sudan', 'start': 23, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Arab League', 'start': 37, 'end': 48}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ambassador', 'start': 1, 'end': 11}]",0.9977839280800667
"*** Odo , Count of Toulouse","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Odo , Count of Toulouse""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Odo , Count of Toulouse""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Odo , Count of Toulouse', 'start': 4, 'end': 27}]",0.9872196113174394
** Sancho II ( 1223–1247 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sancho II""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sancho II""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sancho II', 'start': 3, 'end': 12}]",0.9994650623301514
Wesley Pruden ( 2013 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wesley Pruden""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Wesley Pruden""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wesley Pruden', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9996973277616296
"Previews are scheduled to begin March 13 , 2017 , with an opening date of April 20 , 2017 , at the Shubert Theatre .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Shubert Theatre""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Shubert Theatre""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Shubert Theatre', 'start': 99, 'end': 114}]",0.9558352312565978
"China , Indonesia , Vietnam","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""China""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Indonesia""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Vietnam""}]","{""Location"": [""China"", ""Indonesia"", ""Vietnam""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'China', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Indonesia', 'start': 8, 'end': 17}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Vietnam', 'start': 20, 'end': 27}]",0.999610206004327
Emmett / Furla / Oasis Films,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Emmett / Furla / Oasis Films""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Emmett / Furla / Oasis Films""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Emmett / Furla / Oasis Films', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]",0.9978898753842462
Ekaterina Petaikina / Maxim Kurdyukov,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ekaterina Petaikina""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Maxim Kurdyukov""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ekaterina Petaikina"", ""Maxim Kurdyukov""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ekaterina Petaikina', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Maxim Kurdyukov', 'start': 22, 'end': 37}]",0.9997908868063436
' '' Alberto Puig '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Alberto Puig""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Alberto Puig""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Alberto Puig', 'start': 5, 'end': 17}]",0.9993812184028016
"Ferdinand Albert I , Duke of Brunswick-Lüneburg ( 1636–1687 ) ,","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ferdinand Albert I , Duke of Brunswick-Lüneburg""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ferdinand Albert I , Duke of Brunswick-Lüneburg""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ferdinand Albert I', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Duke of Brunswick-Lüneburg', 'start': 21, 'end': 47}]",0.9992839004765345
Death ( DC Comics ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Death ( DC Comics )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Death ( DC Comics )""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'DC Comics', 'start': 8, 'end': 17}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Death', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]",0.9826783612881682
Goodwater ( 73.3   ),"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Goodwater""}]","{""Location"": [""Goodwater""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Goodwater', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]",0.9967763969804289
' '' Crimean Khanate '' ' – Meñli I Giray ( 1478–1515 ),"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Crimean Khanate""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Meñli I Giray""}]","{""Location"": [""Crimean Khanate""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Meñli I Giray""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Crimean Khanate', 'start': 5, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Meñli I Giray', 'start': 28, 'end': 41}]",0.9996547292315112
Since Texas Instruments was one of the investors in P.A .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Texas Instruments""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Texas Instruments""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Texas', 'start': 6, 'end': 11}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Texas Instruments', 'start': 6, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'P.A.', 'start': 52, 'end': 56}]",0.9045319051782347
Women 's music,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Women 's music""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Women 's music""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': ""Women 's music"", 'start': 0, 'end': 14}]",0.9906379239149165
"FK Viktoria Stadion , Czech Republic ( A )","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""FK Viktoria Stadion""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Czech Republic""}]","{""Location"": [""Czech Republic""], ""Organization"": [""FK Viktoria Stadion""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Czech Republic', 'start': 22, 'end': 36}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'FK Viktoria Stadion', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]",0.9949082792772097
`` One for the Road ( Arctic Monkeys song ) '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""One for the Road ( Arctic Monkeys song )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""One for the Road ( Arctic Monkeys song )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Arctic Monkeys', 'start': 22, 'end': 36}]",0.9517777810060015
Sheik ( disambiguation ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Sheik ( disambiguation )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Sheik ( disambiguation )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Sheik ( disambiguation )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]",0.9771516990083867
Bart-Williams was soon on his way back home only managing eight appearances before having his three-year contract cancelled after only two months of signing it .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bart-Williams""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Bart-Williams""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Bart-Williams', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9995245887076352
M-188 ( Michigan highway ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""M-188 ( Michigan highway )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""M-188 ( Michigan highway )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Michigan', 'start': 8, 'end': 16}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'M-188', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]",0.9101683685982468
"Oliver Neuville 14 , Igor Pamić 6 , Victor Agali 6 , Sławomir Majak 5","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Oliver Neuville""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Igor Pamić""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Victor Agali""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sławomir Majak""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Oliver Neuville"", ""Igor Pamić"", ""Victor Agali"", ""Sławomir Majak""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Oliver Neuville', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Igor Pamić', 'start': 21, 'end': 31}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Victor Agali', 'start': 36, 'end': 48}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sławomir Majak', 'start': 53, 'end': 67}]",0.9994561368069517
"Coffee County , Georgia","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Coffee County , Georgia""}]","{""Location"": [""Coffee County , Georgia""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Coffee County , Georgia', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9877470127710068
"Eleonorenhain : Lenora B,66","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Lenora""}]","{""Location"": [""Lenora""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Eleonorenhain', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lenora B', 'start': 16, 'end': 24}]",0.9869975144536193
Solicitor General for Scotland — Lesley Thomson,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Solicitor General for Scotland""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lesley Thomson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Solicitor General for Scotland"", ""Lesley Thomson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Solicitor General for Scotland', 'start': 0, 'end': 30}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lesley Thomson', 'start': 33, 'end': 47}]",0.9996420603059172
Thirumudi N. Sethuraman,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thirumudi N. Sethuraman""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Thirumudi N. Sethuraman""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thirumudi N. Sethuraman', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9997644584219408
CAE Global Academy Phoenix,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""CAE Global Academy Phoenix""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""CAE Global Academy Phoenix""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Phoenix', 'start': 19, 'end': 26}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'CAE Global Academy', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}]",0.9946878413355043
This was Mariano Moreno’s a.k.a .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Mariano Moreno’s""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Mariano Moreno’s""]}",no,[],0.9937199519521764
Ölürüm Sana ( album ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Ölürüm Sana ( album )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Ölürüm Sana ( album )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Ölürüm Sana ( album )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]",0.9916583211099167
"`` Boogie Wonderland '' – Earth , Wind and Fire","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Boogie Wonderland""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Earth , Wind and Fire""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Boogie Wonderland"", ""Earth , Wind and Fire""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Earth , Wind and Fire', 'start': 26, 'end': 47}]",0.9721125225769728
Florynce Kennedy also hosted a regular opinion segment .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Florynce Kennedy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Florynce Kennedy""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Florynce Kennedy', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]",0.999723784584504
' '' 1985 Major League Baseball All-Star Game at the Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome in Minneapolis,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1985 Major League Baseball All-Star Game""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Minneapolis""}]","{""Location"": [""Minneapolis""], ""Organization"": [""1985 Major League Baseball All-Star Game"", ""Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Minneapolis', 'start': 85, 'end': 96}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': '1985 Major League Baseball All-Star Game', 'start': 5, 'end': 45}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome', 'start': 53, 'end': 81}]",0.9875147128425157
William Heseltine ( acting ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William Heseltine""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""William Heseltine""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William Heseltine', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]",0.9969526221720242
"It was included on their May 2014 album Barrel Brothers '' , released on EMPIRE Recordings .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Barrel Brothers""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""EMPIRE Recordings""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Barrel Brothers"", ""EMPIRE Recordings""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'EMPIRE Recordings', 'start': 73, 'end': 90}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Barrel Brothers', 'start': 40, 'end': 55}]",0.8806041868334994
Communes of the Aube department,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Communes of the Aube department""}]","{""Location"": [""Communes of the Aube department""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Communes of the Aube department', 'start': 0, 'end': 31}]",0.9995448975716409
'' Cannonball '' by The Breeders ( co-directed by Kim Gordon ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Cannonball""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""The Breeders""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kim Gordon""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Cannonball"", ""The Breeders""], ""Person"": [""Kim Gordon""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'The Breeders', 'start': 20, 'end': 32}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kim Gordon', 'start': 50, 'end': 60}]",0.9459972891643977
José San Román,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""José San Román""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""José San Román""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'José San Román', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}]",0.9996086144031109
Decadent poet Ernest Dowson was his great-nephew .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Decadent""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ernest Dowson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Decadent""], ""Person"": [""Ernest Dowson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ernest Dowson', 'start': 14, 'end': 27}]",0.9993189345854074
From Enslavement to Obliteration,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""From Enslavement to Obliteration""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""From Enslavement to Obliteration""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'From Enslavement to Obliteration', 'start': 0, 'end': 32}]",0.9913057485007202
"** Mitsubishi Fuso Truck of America , Inc . ( MFTA -- a subsidiary of MFTBC )","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Mitsubishi Fuso Truck of America , Inc .""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Mitsubishi Fuso Truck of America , Inc .""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Mitsubishi Fuso Truck of America', 'start': 3, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'MFTA', 'start': 46, 'end': 50}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'MFTBC', 'start': 70, 'end': 75}]",0.9675313405221028
75th Guards Rifle Division,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""75th Guards Rifle Division""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""75th Guards Rifle Division""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '75th Guards Rifle Division', 'start': 0, 'end': 26}]",0.9997217840699817
"Alex Stiebling - ( WEC , Pancrase , PRIDE , UFC , WFA )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Alex Stiebling""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""WEC""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Pancrase""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""PRIDE""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""UFC""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""WFA""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""WEC"", ""Pancrase"", ""PRIDE"", ""UFC"", ""WFA""], ""Person"": [""Alex Stiebling""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'WEC', 'start': 19, 'end': 22}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Pancrase', 'start': 25, 'end': 33}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'PRIDE', 'start': 36, 'end': 41}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'UFC', 'start': 44, 'end': 47}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'WFA', 'start': 50, 'end': 53}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Alex Stiebling', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}]",0.9995232704433695
' '' Neftalí Feliz '' ' ( 30 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Neftalí Feliz""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Neftalí Feliz""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Neftalí Feliz', 'start': 5, 'end': 18}]",0.9985899399541572
"Ilija Bozoljac and Filip Krajinović won the title , defeating Nikoloz Basilashvili and Alexander Bury in the final , 6–1 , 6–2 .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ilija Bozoljac""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Filip Krajinović""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Nikoloz Basilashvili""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Alexander Bury""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ilija Bozoljac"", ""Filip Krajinović"", ""Nikoloz Basilashvili"", ""Alexander Bury""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ilija Bozoljac', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Filip Krajinović', 'start': 19, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Nikoloz Basilashvili', 'start': 62, 'end': 82}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Alexander Bury', 'start': 87, 'end': 101}]",0.9994932901250777
"Ealdred , king of the Hwicce","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ealdred , king of the Hwicce""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ealdred , king of the Hwicce""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Hwicce', 'start': 22, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ealdred', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}]",0.9745301115560757
East Fork Des Moines River,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""East Fork Des Moines River""}]","{""Location"": [""East Fork Des Moines River""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'East Fork Des Moines River', 'start': 0, 'end': 26}]",0.9997213034930886
National Autonomous University of Mexico,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""National Autonomous University of Mexico""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""National Autonomous University of Mexico""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'National Autonomous University of Mexico', 'start': 0, 'end': 40}]",0.9816676698982307
"The album was co-produced , recorded and mixed by Steve Addabbo ( Suzanne Vega ) .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Steve Addabbo""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Suzanne Vega""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Steve Addabbo"", ""Suzanne Vega""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Steve Addabbo', 'start': 50, 'end': 63}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Suzanne Vega', 'start': 66, 'end': 78}]",0.9990323910541355
"Rosie Casals Martina Navratilova6–4 , 7–5","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Rosie Casals""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Martina Navratilova6–4""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Rosie Casals""], ""Person"": [""Martina Navratilova6–4""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rosie Casals', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Martina Navratilova', 'start': 13, 'end': 32}]",0.97979118076599
The Great Wide Open '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""The Great Wide Open""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""The Great Wide Open""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'The Great Wide Open', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]",0.969809786620687
Liverpool Sound Collage,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Liverpool Sound Collage""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Liverpool Sound Collage""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Liverpool Sound Collage', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]",0.9994881753936814
Dwight Howard ( 26 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Dwight Howard""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Dwight Howard""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Dwight Howard', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]",0.9995223431560367
"Bon Gir , Sistan and Baluchestan","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bon Gir , Sistan and Baluchestan""}]","{""Location"": [""Bon Gir , Sistan and Baluchestan""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Bon Gir', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Sistan and Baluchestan', 'start': 10, 'end': 32}]",0.9444411997350701
