Text,IndividualLabels,CategorizedLabels,llm_labeled_successfully,llm_label
: Kanye West featuring Jamie Foxx — `` Gold Digger '' ( 2005 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kanye West""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jamie Foxx""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Gold Digger""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Gold Digger""], ""Person"": [""Kanye West"", ""Jamie Foxx""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kanye West', 'start': 2, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jamie Foxx', 'start': 23, 'end': 33}]"
Blacktown railway station,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Blacktown railway station""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Blacktown railway station""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Blacktown', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'railway station', 'start': 10, 'end': 25}]"
"'' Mycalesis perseus lalassis '' ( Hewitson , 1864 )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Mycalesis perseus lalassis""}]","{""Location"": [""Mycalesis perseus lalassis""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mycalesis perseus lalassis', 'start': 3, 'end': 29}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hewitson', 'start': 35, 'end': 43}]"
Jonny Lee Miller - Eli Stone '',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jonny Lee Miller""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Eli Stone""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Eli Stone""], ""Person"": [""Jonny Lee Miller""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Eli Stone', 'start': 19, 'end': 28}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jonny Lee Miller', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]"
Tambourissa cocottensis '' Lorence,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Tambourissa cocottensis""}]","{""Location"": [""Tambourissa cocottensis""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tambourissa cocottensis', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lorence', 'start': 27, 'end': 34}]"
Admission to the bar in the United States,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Admission to the bar in the United States""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Admission to the bar in the United States""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'United States', 'start': 28, 'end': 41}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Admission to the bar', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]"
Willy Unger of 11 .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Willy Unger""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Willy Unger""]}",no,[]
"Much construction was undertaken during this period , such as the building of Palermo Cathedral .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Palermo Cathedral""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Palermo Cathedral""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Palermo', 'start': 78, 'end': 85}]"
List of The O.C. characters,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""List of The O.C. characters""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""List of The O.C. characters""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of The O.C. characters', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}]"
"Cardiff Royal Infirmary , Roath , Cardiff","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Cardiff Royal Infirmary""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Roath , Cardiff""}]","{""Location"": [""Roath , Cardiff""], ""Organization"": [""Cardiff Royal Infirmary""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Cardiff', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Roath', 'start': 26, 'end': 31}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Cardiff', 'start': 34, 'end': 41}]"
Roger Houdet 9 June 1958 – 27 May 1959,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Roger Houdet""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Roger Houdet""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Roger Houdet', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]"
List of Oz ( TV series ) characters,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""List of Oz ( TV series ) characters""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""List of Oz ( TV series ) characters""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of Oz ( TV series ) characters', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]"
: '' Jack and Diane '' by John Mellencamp - '' ( Top 11 ) '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jack and Diane""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Mellencamp""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Jack and Diane""], ""Person"": [""John Mellencamp""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Top 11', 'start': 49, 'end': 55}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jack', 'start': 5, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Diane', 'start': 14, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Mellencamp', 'start': 26, 'end': 41}]"
List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Antarctic', 'start': 8, 'end': 17}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'sub-Antarctic', 'start': 22, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'List of Antarctic and sub-Antarctic islands', 'start': 0, 'end': 43}]"
Yukon New Democratic Party,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Yukon New Democratic Party""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Yukon New Democratic Party""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Yukon', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Yukon New Democratic Party', 'start': 0, 'end': 26}]"
1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '1st Foreign Legion Cavalry Regiment', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}]"
John Reid ( ''27 July 1998 – 17 May 1999 '' ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Reid""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""John Reid""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Reid', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]"
Annweiler am Trifels,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Annweiler am Trifels""}]","{""Location"": [""Annweiler am Trifels""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Annweiler am Trifels', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]"
Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': ""Manuel `` Flaco '' Ibáñez"", 'start': 0, 'end': 25}]"
`` Moments and Mine '' 7 '' single ( 1981 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Moments and Mine""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Moments and Mine""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Moments and Mine', 'start': 3, 'end': 19}]"
2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': '2008–09 Beşiktaş J.K. season', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]"
C]] ) ' '' Akritas Chlorakas '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Akritas Chlorakas""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Akritas Chlorakas""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Akritas Chlorakas', 'start': 11, 'end': 28}]"
Farmers ' Almanac '' ( 1818–present ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Farmers ' Almanac""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Farmers ' Almanac""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': ""Farmers ' Almanac"", 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]"
He was betrayed in 1931 and arrested by the Kuomintang in Tianjin in 1931 .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kuomintang""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Tianjin""}]","{""Location"": [""Tianjin""], ""Organization"": [""Kuomintang""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Tianjin', 'start': 58, 'end': 65}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Kuomintang', 'start': 44, 'end': 54}]"
It is found in Peru .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Peru""}]","{""Location"": [""Peru""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Peru', 'start': 15, 'end': 19}]"
Steve Hindalong - producer,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Steve Hindalong""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Steve Hindalong""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Steve Hindalong', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}]"
Han Suyin gives a detailed account of their overthrow :,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Han Suyin""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Han Suyin""]}",no,[]
"Bishop John J. Kinney ( November 9 , 1976 - June 28 , 1982 ) appointed Bishop of Bismarck , Bishop of Saint Cloud ( 1995 )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bishop John J. Kinney""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bishop of Bismarck""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Bishop of Saint Cloud""}]","{""Location"": [""Bishop of Bismarck"", ""Bishop of Saint Cloud""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Bishop John J. Kinney""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Bismarck', 'start': 81, 'end': 89}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Saint Cloud', 'start': 102, 'end': 113}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John J. Kinney', 'start': 7, 'end': 21}]"
"Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin""}]","{""Location"": [""Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Wilson , Eau Claire County , Wisconsin', 'start': 0, 'end': 38}]"
' '' Sydney Theatre Company '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sydney Theatre Company""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sydney Theatre Company""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Sydney Theatre Company', 'start': 5, 'end': 27}]"
His first recording of the song was included on his 2005 album Time Well Wasted '' .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Time Well Wasted""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Time Well Wasted""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Time Well Wasted', 'start': 63, 'end': 79}]"
Goes to Jhansi ( JHS ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jhansi""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Jhansi""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Jhansi ( JHS )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]"
** '' Kashiwa Reysol '' ' 3–2 ( 2–0 ) Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kashiwa Reysol""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Kashiwa Reysol"", ""Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Kashiwa Reysol', 'start': 6, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Jeonbuk Hyundai Motors', 'start': 38, 'end': 60}]"
"He was born in Merritt Island , Florida .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Merritt Island , Florida""}]","{""Location"": [""Merritt Island , Florida""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Merritt Island , Florida', 'start': 15, 'end': 39}]"
Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton""}]","{""Location"": [""Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Edmonton', 'start': 0, 'end': 38}]"
"He scored the first two touchdowns of his career on September 23 , 2007 in a 24–3 win against the St. Louis Rams .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""St. Louis Rams""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""St. Louis Rams""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'St. Louis Rams', 'start': 98, 'end': 112}]"
"It was founded in 2013 by Jean Colombera , a member of the Chamber of Deputies that had been elected for the Alternative Democratic Reform Party at the 2009 election .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Jean Colombera""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chamber of Deputies""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Alternative Democratic Reform Party""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""2009 election""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Chamber of Deputies"", ""Alternative Democratic Reform Party"", ""2009 election""], ""Person"": [""Jean Colombera""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Alternative Democratic Reform Party', 'start': 109, 'end': 144}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Jean Colombera', 'start': 26, 'end': 40}]"
Ashley Tappin ( 55.47 ) Erin Phenix ( 56.12 ) Courtney Shealy ( 54.99 ) Amy Van Dyken ( 54.40 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ashley Tappin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Erin Phenix""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Courtney Shealy""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Amy Van Dyken""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ashley Tappin"", ""Erin Phenix"", ""Courtney Shealy"", ""Amy Van Dyken""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ashley Tappin', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Erin Phenix', 'start': 24, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Courtney Shealy', 'start': 46, 'end': 61}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Amy Van Dyken', 'start': 72, 'end': 85}]"
Romy Kermer / Rolf Österreich,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Romy Kermer""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Rolf Österreich""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Romy Kermer"", ""Rolf Österreich""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Romy Kermer', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rolf Österreich', 'start': 14, 'end': 29}]"
"Gates-Chili High School , Gates","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Gates-Chili High School""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Gates""}]","{""Location"": [""Gates""], ""Organization"": [""Gates-Chili High School""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Gates-Chili High School', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Gates', 'start': 0, 'end': 5}]"
Riki Lindhome ( 5 appearances ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Riki Lindhome""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Riki Lindhome""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Riki Lindhome', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]"
Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Raindrops Keep Fallin ' on My Head""], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
"He died in Hermanus , Western Cape , South Africa , aged 68 , and was buried in Israel .","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Hermanus""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Western Cape""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""South Africa""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Israel""}]","{""Location"": [""Hermanus"", ""Western Cape"", ""South Africa"", ""Israel""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Hermanus , Western Cape , South Africa', 'start': 11, 'end': 49}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Israel', 'start': 80, 'end': 86}]"
for the treatment of Type 1 Diabetes .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Type 1 Diabetes""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Type 1 Diabetes""], ""Person"": []}",yes,[]
He died at his home at Earls Court and was buried at West Norwood Cemetery .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Earls Court""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""West Norwood Cemetery""}]","{""Location"": [""Earls Court""], ""Organization"": [""West Norwood Cemetery""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Earls Court', 'start': 23, 'end': 34}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'West Norwood Cemetery', 'start': 53, 'end': 74}]"
Both teams had the chance to play in Super Bowl XLIX .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Super Bowl XLIX""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Super Bowl XLIX""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Super Bowl XLIX', 'start': 37, 'end': 52}]"
Its closest competitor is the Encash Network Service .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Encash Network Service""}]","{""Location"": [""Encash Network Service""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Encash Network Service', 'start': 30, 'end': 52}]"
"Turning Stone Casino , Verona , New York , United States","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Turning Stone Casino""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Verona , New York""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""United States""}]","{""Location"": [""Verona , New York"", ""United States""], ""Organization"": [""Turning Stone Casino""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Verona , New York , United States', 'start': 23, 'end': 56}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Turning Stone Casino', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}]"
"Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia""}]","{""Location"": [""Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Crown , Monongalia County , West Virginia', 'start': 0, 'end': 41}]"
"Tang Yik Chun , Lai Chun Ho , Ng Ka Fung , Tsui Chi Ho","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tang Yik Chun""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lai Chun Ho""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ng Ka Fung""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tsui Chi Ho""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Tang Yik Chun"", ""Lai Chun Ho"", ""Ng Ka Fung"", ""Tsui Chi Ho""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tang Yik Chun', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lai Chun Ho', 'start': 16, 'end': 27}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ng Ka Fung', 'start': 30, 'end': 40}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Tsui Chi Ho', 'start': 43, 'end': 54}]"
'' 1999 '' ( Prince ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""1999""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Prince""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""1999""], ""Person"": [""Prince""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Prince', 'start': 13, 'end': 19}]"
Hay River Reserve,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Hay River Reserve""}]","{""Location"": [""Hay River Reserve""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Hay River Reserve', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}]"
'' Heathcliff '' ( 1980 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Heathcliff""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Heathcliff""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Heathcliff', 'start': 3, 'end': 13}]"
Galician Academy ( private ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Galician Academy""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Galician Academy""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Galician Academy', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]"
"'' Thysanoplusia orichalcea '' ( Fabricius , 1775 )","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Thysanoplusia orichalcea""}]","{""Location"": [""Thysanoplusia orichalcea""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Fabricius', 'start': 33, 'end': 42}]"
He became George III 's Chaplain-in-Ordinary .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""George III""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chaplain-in-Ordinary""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""George III"", ""Chaplain-in-Ordinary""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Chaplain-in-Ordinary', 'start': 24, 'end': 44}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'George III', 'start': 10, 'end': 20}]"
Mark King ( born 1958 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Mark King""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Mark King""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Mark King', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]"
Paul Tsongas - 209 ( 4.98   ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Paul Tsongas""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Paul Tsongas""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Paul Tsongas', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]"
'' Papilio polyxenes '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Papilio polyxenes""}]","{""Location"": [""Papilio polyxenes""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
"'' Heliothis nubigera '' Herrich-Schäffer , 1851","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Heliothis nubigera""}]","{""Location"": [""Heliothis nubigera""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Herrich-Schäffer', 'start': 25, 'end': 41}]"
' '' Andaman and Nicobar Islands '' ',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Andaman and Nicobar Islands""}]","{""Location"": [""Andaman and Nicobar Islands""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Andaman and Nicobar Islands', 'start': 5, 'end': 32}]"
"Glasston , North Dakota","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Glasston , North Dakota""}]","{""Location"": [""Glasston , North Dakota""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Glasston , North Dakota', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]"
St. Martin River,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""St. Martin River""}]","{""Location"": [""St. Martin River""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'St. Martin River', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}]"
"The album reached number one halfway through its first week , with over 2,500 copies sold ( rivalling Adele , Bruno Mars and Ed Sheeran ) .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Adele""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bruno Mars""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ed Sheeran""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Adele"", ""Bruno Mars"", ""Ed Sheeran""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Adele', 'start': 102, 'end': 107}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Bruno Mars', 'start': 110, 'end': 120}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ed Sheeran', 'start': 125, 'end': 135}]"
Winx Club '' ( 2005–08 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Winx Club""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Winx Club""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Winx Club', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}]"
"Organized at Fort Craig , it was mustered on 23 November 1861 and served until 28 February 1862 .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Fort Craig""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Fort Craig""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Fort Craig', 'start': 13, 'end': 23}]"
Rudy Wurlitzer as Tom O'Folliard,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Rudy Wurlitzer""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Tom O'Folliard""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Rudy Wurlitzer"", ""Tom O'Folliard""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Rudy Wurlitzer', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': ""Tom O'Folliard"", 'start': 18, 'end': 32}]"
Conrad Aiken - W. H. Auden - George Barker - John Berryman - Robert Bly - Hart Crane - E. E. Cummings - Donald Davie - James Dickey - H. D . - Keith Douglas - Richard Eberhart - T. S. Eliot - William Empson - David Gascoyne - W. S. Graham - Robert Graves - Thom Gunn - John Heath-Stubbs - Geoffrey Hill - Gerard Manley Hopkins - Ted Hughes - T. E. Hulme - David Jones - Philip Larkin - D. H. Lawrence - Denise Levertov - C. Day Lewis - Robert Lowell - Norman MacCaig - Hugh MacDiarmid - Louis MacNeice - Charles Madge - W. S. Merwin - Christopher Middleton - Harold Monro - Marianne Moore - Edwin Muir - Howard Nemerov - Charles Olson - Wilfred Owen - Sylvia Plath - Ezra Pound - F. T. Prince - Kathleen Raine - John Crowe Ransom - Herbert Read - Laura Riding - Anne Ridler - Michael Roberts - Theodore Roethke - Isaac Rosenberg - Louis Simpson - Edith Sitwell - W. D. Snodgrass - Stephen Spender - Wallace Stevens - Allen Tate - Dylan Thomas - R. S. Thomas - Charles Tomlinson - Vernon Watkins - Richard Wilbur - William Carlos Williams - James Wright - W. B. Yeats,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Conrad Aiken""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. H. Auden""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""George Barker""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Berryman""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Bly""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hart Crane""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""E.""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""E. Cummings""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Donald Davie""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""James Dickey""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""H. D .""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Keith Douglas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Richard Eberhart""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""T. S. Eliot""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William Empson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""David Gascoyne""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. S. Graham""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Graves""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thom Gunn""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Heath-Stubbs""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Geoffrey Hill""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Gerard Manley Hopkins""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ted Hughes""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""T. E. Hulme""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""David Jones""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Philip Larkin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""D. H. Lawrence""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Denise Levertov""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""C. Day Lewis""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Robert Lowell""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Norman MacCaig""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hugh MacDiarmid""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Louis MacNeice""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Madge""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. S. Merwin""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Christopher Middleton""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Harold Monro""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Marianne Moore""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Edwin Muir""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Howard Nemerov""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Olson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wilfred Owen""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sylvia Plath""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ezra Pound""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""F. T. Prince""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Kathleen Raine""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""John Crowe Ransom""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Herbert Read""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Laura Riding""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Anne Ridler""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Michael Roberts""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Theodore Roethke""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Isaac Rosenberg""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Louis Simpson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Edith Sitwell""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. D. Snodgrass""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Stephen Spender""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Wallace Stevens""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Allen Tate""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Dylan Thomas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""R. S. Thomas""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Charles Tomlinson""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Vernon Watkins""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Richard Wilbur""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""William Carlos Williams""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""James Wright""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""W. B. Yeats""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""H. D ."", ""C. Day Lewis""], ""Person"": [""Conrad Aiken"", ""W. H. Auden"", ""George Barker"", ""John Berryman"", ""Robert Bly"", ""Hart Crane"", ""E."", ""E. Cummings"", ""Donald Davie"", ""James Dickey"", ""Keith Douglas"", ""Richard Eberhart"", ""T. S. Eliot"", ""William Empson"", ""David Gascoyne"", ""W. S. Graham"", ""Robert Graves"", ""Thom Gunn"", ""John Heath-Stubbs"", ""Geoffrey Hill"", ""Gerard Manley Hopkins"", ""Ted Hughes"", ""T. E. Hulme"", ""David Jones"", ""Philip Larkin"", ""D. H. Lawrence"", ""Denise Levertov"", ""Robert Lowell"", ""Norman MacCaig"", ""Hugh MacDiarmid"", ""Louis MacNeice"", ""Charles Madge"", ""W. S. Merwin"", ""Christopher Middleton"", ""Harold Monro"", ""Marianne Moore"", ""Edwin Muir"", ""Howard Nemerov"", ""Charles Olson"", ""Wilfred Owen"", ""Sylvia Plath"", ""Ezra Pound"", ""F. T. Prince"", ""Kathleen Raine"", ""John Crowe Ransom"", ""Herbert Read"", ""Laura Riding"", ""Anne Ridler"", ""Michael Roberts"", ""Theodore Roethke"", ""Isaac Rosenberg"", ""Louis Simpson"", ""Edith Sitwell"", ""W. D. Snodgrass"", ""Stephen Spender"", ""Wallace Stevens"", ""Allen Tate"", ""Dylan Thomas"", ""R. S. Thomas"", ""Charles Tomlinson"", ""Vernon Watkins"", ""Richard Wilbur"", ""William Carlos Williams"", ""James Wright"", ""W. B. Yeats""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Conrad Aiken', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. H. Auden', 'start': 15, 'end': 26}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'George Barker', 'start': 29, 'end': 42}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Berryman', 'start': 45, 'end': 58}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Bly', 'start': 61, 'end': 71}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hart Crane', 'start': 74, 'end': 84}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'E. E. Cummings', 'start': 87, 'end': 101}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Donald Davie', 'start': 104, 'end': 116}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'James Dickey', 'start': 119, 'end': 131}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'H. D.', 'start': 134, 'end': 139}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Keith Douglas', 'start': 143, 'end': 156}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Richard Eberhart', 'start': 159, 'end': 175}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'T. S. Eliot', 'start': 178, 'end': 189}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William Empson', 'start': 192, 'end': 206}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'David Gascoyne', 'start': 209, 'end': 223}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. S. Graham', 'start': 226, 'end': 238}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Graves', 'start': 241, 'end': 254}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thom Gunn', 'start': 257, 'end': 266}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Heath-Stubbs', 'start': 269, 'end': 286}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Geoffrey Hill', 'start': 289, 'end': 302}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Gerard Manley Hopkins', 'start': 305, 'end': 326}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ted Hughes', 'start': 329, 'end': 339}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'T. E. Hulme', 'start': 342, 'end': 353}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'David Jones', 'start': 356, 'end': 367}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Philip Larkin', 'start': 370, 'end': 383}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'D. H. Lawrence', 'start': 386, 'end': 400}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Denise Levertov', 'start': 403, 'end': 418}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'C. Day Lewis', 'start': 421, 'end': 433}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Robert Lowell', 'start': 436, 'end': 449}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Norman MacCaig', 'start': 452, 'end': 466}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hugh MacDiarmid', 'start': 469, 'end': 484}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Louis MacNeice', 'start': 487, 'end': 501}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Madge', 'start': 504, 'end': 517}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. S. Merwin', 'start': 520, 'end': 532}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Christopher Middleton', 'start': 535, 'end': 556}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Harold Monro', 'start': 559, 'end': 571}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Marianne Moore', 'start': 574, 'end': 588}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Edwin Muir', 'start': 591, 'end': 601}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Howard Nemerov', 'start': 604, 'end': 618}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Olson', 'start': 621, 'end': 634}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wilfred Owen', 'start': 637, 'end': 649}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sylvia Plath', 'start': 652, 'end': 664}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ezra Pound', 'start': 667, 'end': 677}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'F. T. Prince', 'start': 680, 'end': 692}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Kathleen Raine', 'start': 695, 'end': 709}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'John Crowe Ransom', 'start': 712, 'end': 729}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Herbert Read', 'start': 732, 'end': 744}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Laura Riding', 'start': 747, 'end': 759}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Anne Ridler', 'start': 762, 'end': 773}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Michael Roberts', 'start': 776, 'end': 791}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Theodore Roethke', 'start': 794, 'end': 810}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Isaac Rosenberg', 'start': 813, 'end': 828}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Louis Simpson', 'start': 831, 'end': 844}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Edith Sitwell', 'start': 847, 'end': 860}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. D. Snodgrass', 'start': 863, 'end': 878}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Stephen Spender', 'start': 881, 'end': 896}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Wallace Stevens', 'start': 899, 'end': 914}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Allen Tate', 'start': 917, 'end': 927}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Dylan Thomas', 'start': 930, 'end': 942}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'R. S. Thomas', 'start': 945, 'end': 957}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Charles Tomlinson', 'start': 960, 'end': 977}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Vernon Watkins', 'start': 980, 'end': 994}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Richard Wilbur', 'start': 997, 'end': 1011}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'William Carlos Williams', 'start': 1014, 'end': 1037}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'James Wright', 'start': 1040, 'end': 1052}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'W. B. Yeats', 'start': 1055, 'end': 1066}]"
*Seated figure of Sir Walter Scott for Powderham Castle ( 1832 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Sir Walter Scott""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Powderham Castle""}]","{""Location"": [""Powderham Castle""], ""Organization"": [""Sir Walter Scott""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Powderham Castle', 'start': 39, 'end': 55}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sir Walter Scott', 'start': 18, 'end': 34}]"
"Sandy Ridge , North Carolina","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Sandy Ridge , North Carolina""}]","{""Location"": [""Sandy Ridge , North Carolina""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Sandy Ridge , North Carolina', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}]"
Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Ashok Kumar ( Telugu actor )""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ashok Kumar', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}]"
Thomas Gabriel Fischer leaves Celtic Frost in April .,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Thomas Gabriel Fischer""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Celtic Frost""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Celtic Frost""], ""Person"": [""Thomas Gabriel Fischer""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Celtic Frost', 'start': 30, 'end': 42}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Thomas Gabriel Fischer', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}]"
'' Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ? '',"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ?""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Can You Teach My Alligator Manners ?""], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
Otto Geßler ( Acting ) ( 1875–1955 ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Otto Geßler""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Otto Geßler""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Acting', 'start': 14, 'end': 20}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Otto Geßler', 'start': 0, 'end': 11}]"
: On Lifetime Channel,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Lifetime Channel""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Lifetime Channel""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Lifetime Channel', 'start': 5, 'end': 21}]"
RCI 367 ( Radio Canada International ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Radio Canada International""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Radio Canada International""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'RCI 367', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Radio Canada International', 'start': 10, 'end': 36}]"
"Sir Robert Robinson , from 1930 to 1954 .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Sir Robert Robinson""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Sir Robert Robinson""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sir Robert Robinson', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]"
"Hutton , Frederick Wollaston .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Hutton , Frederick Wollaston""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Hutton , Frederick Wollaston""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Hutton', 'start': 0, 'end': 6}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Frederick Wollaston', 'start': 9, 'end': 28}]"
'' Macrobathra monoclina '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Macrobathra monoclina""}]","{""Location"": [""Macrobathra monoclina""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
He one of eleven founding members of the American Society of Landscape Architects in 1899 and was active in the City Beautiful Movement '' .,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""American Society of Landscape Architects""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""City Beautiful Movement""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""American Society of Landscape Architects"", ""City Beautiful Movement""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'American Society of Landscape Architects', 'start': 41, 'end': 81}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'City Beautiful Movement', 'start': 112, 'end': 135}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'He', 'start': 0, 'end': 2}]"
"Alberto Mancini won in the final 7–5 , 2–6 , 7–6 , 7–5 against Boris Becker .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Alberto Mancini""}, {""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Boris Becker""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Alberto Mancini"", ""Boris Becker""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Alberto Mancini', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Boris Becker', 'start': 63, 'end': 75}]"
'' Congoharpax aberrans '',"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Congoharpax aberrans""}]","{""Location"": [""Congoharpax aberrans""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
Kaohsiung Museum of Labor,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Kaohsiung Museum of Labor""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Kaohsiung Museum of Labor""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Kaohsiung', 'start': 0, 'end': 9}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Museum of Labor', 'start': 10, 'end': 25}]"
"Benigno S. Aquino , Jr . , August 21 , 2004 ( posthumous )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Benigno S. Aquino , Jr .""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Benigno S. Aquino , Jr .""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Benigno S. Aquino , Jr.', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}]"
Lina Carstens ( 1892–1978 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lina Carstens""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Lina Carstens""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lina Carstens', 'start': 0, 'end': 13}]"
"**On June 26 against the Chicago Cubs , he got his 2000th career hit with a home run in the second inning .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Chicago Cubs""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Chicago Cubs""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Chicago Cubs', 'start': 25, 'end': 37}]"
Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 46}]"
Carmelita Tropicana - Performance artist,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Carmelita Tropicana""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Carmelita Tropicana""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Carmelita Tropicana', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}]"
University of Giessen,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""University of Giessen""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""University of Giessen""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'University of Giessen', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}]"
Bradley Beal ( 34 ),"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Bradley Beal""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Bradley Beal""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Bradley Beal', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}]"
"Five Borders shops in Oxford Street , Llantrisant , Blanchardstown , Swindon and London Colney were closed in July 2009 and replaced by New Look .","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Oxford Street""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Llantrisant""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Blanchardstown""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Swindon""}, {""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""London Colney""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""New Look""}]","{""Location"": [""Llantrisant"", ""Blanchardstown"", ""Swindon"", ""London Colney""], ""Organization"": [""Oxford Street"", ""New Look""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Oxford Street', 'start': 22, 'end': 35}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Llantrisant', 'start': 38, 'end': 49}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Blanchardstown', 'start': 52, 'end': 66}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'Swindon', 'start': 69, 'end': 76}, {'type': 'Location', 'text': 'London Colney', 'start': 81, 'end': 94}, {'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'New Look', 'start': 136, 'end': 144}]"
"Lord Zetland , the Secretary of State for India , was presiding over the meeting and was wounded .","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Lord Zetland""}, {""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Secretary of State for India""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Secretary of State for India""], ""Person"": [""Lord Zetland""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Lord Zetland', 'start': 0, 'end': 12}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Secretary of State for India', 'start': 19, 'end': 47}]"
Night At The Museum,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Night At The Museum""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Night At The Museum""], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
Vepris trifoliolata '' ( Engl .,"[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Vepris trifoliolata""}]","{""Location"": [""Vepris trifoliolata""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
** `` Back for More '' – Sandwich,"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Sandwich""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Sandwich""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Back for More', 'start': 6, 'end': 19}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Sandwich', 'start': 25, 'end': 33}]"
"Crested caracara , ''Caracara cheriway '' ( A )","[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Crested caracara""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Crested caracara""], ""Person"": []}",no,[]
"8 July — Annie Shepherd Swan , writer ( died 1943 )","[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Annie Shepherd Swan""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Annie Shepherd Swan""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Annie Shepherd Swan', 'start': 9, 'end': 28}]"
Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi,"[{""Description"": ""Person"", ""Text"": ""Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": [""Vandino and Ugolino Vivaldi""]}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Vandino', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}, {'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Ugolino Vivaldi', 'start': 12, 'end': 27}]"
Inhaler ( album ),"[{""Description"": ""Organization"", ""Text"": ""Inhaler ( album )""}]","{""Location"": [], ""Organization"": [""Inhaler ( album )""], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Organization', 'text': 'Inhaler ( album )', 'start': -1, 'end': -1}]"
"'' Autosticha pelodes '' Meyrick , 1928","[{""Description"": ""Location"", ""Text"": ""Autosticha pelodes""}]","{""Location"": [""Autosticha pelodes""], ""Organization"": [], ""Person"": []}",yes,"[{'type': 'Person', 'text': 'Meyrick', 'start': 25, 'end': 32}]"
